[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Security professionals are tasked with the protection of persons, property, and",
		"correct": "Information",
		"options": [
			"Government buildings",
			"Employee belongings",
			"Information",
			"Military locations"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "Individuals holding an individual security licence in the province of Alberta may not refer to themselves as:",
		"correct": "Peace officers",
		"options": [
			"Security professionals",
			"Loss prevention workers",
			"Peace officers",
			"Watchpersons"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": " Professionalism is best demonstrated by:",
		"correct": "Peace officers",
		"options": [
			"Your conduct and deportment",
			"Loss prevention workers",
			"Peace officers",
			"Watchpersons"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "Your conduct and deportment __________________ utilized by licensed security professionals must be authorized by the Registrar",
		"correct": "Batons",
		"options": ["Batons", "Reporting forms", "Post orders", "Safety equipment"]
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "The notes in your notebook will help you:",
		"correct": "Prepare reports for your employer and others",
		"options": [
			"Prepare reports for your employer and others",
			"Avoid court testimony",
			"Obtain a security licence in another    classification",
			"Communicate non-verbally "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "Writing profanity in your notebook is:",
		"correct": "Acceptable when you are quoting verbatim",
		"options": [
			"Never appropriate",
			"Acceptable when you are quoting verbatim",
			"Inadmissible in court",
			"Prohibited under the Security Services and Investigator’s Act"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "A statement is usually gathered as part of the _____________ process.",
		"correct": "Interview",
		"options": [
			"Use of force",
			"Interview",
			"Verbal communication",
			"Post-order"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "When you lose your security licence, you must file a written report to:",
		"correct": "The Registrar of Security programs",
		"options": [
			"The police",
			"The Registrar of Security programs",
			"Your supervisor",
			"The client where you lost your licence"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "A security professional in the province of Alberta must be, at minimum, _________years of age.",
		"correct": "18",
		"options": ["16", "18", "19", "21"]
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "A licensed security professional may perform the following tasks:",
		"correct": "All of the above",
		"options": [
			"Monitoring of alarm systems",
			"Arrest of persons found committing a crime",
			"Responding to emergencies",
			"Conducting physical searches of purses,   backpacks, and other personal items",
			"All of the above"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "Protecting information may include limiting access of persons to computer equipment and data.",
		"correct": "True",
		"options": ["True", "False"]
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"question": "An individual holding a security licence is licensed to work as a private detective when:",
		"correct": "Never",
		"options": [
			"Directed by the licensee’s employer",
			"The security professional is directed to  protect information",
			"The work of another employee must be covered due to illness or vacation",
			"Never"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 13,
		"question": "Uniform requirements for licensed security professionals are designated by:",
		"correct": "The Security Services and Investigators Act",
		"options": [
			"The Employment Standards Code and  Regulation",
			"The Security Operations Standards Council",
			"The Security Services and Investigators Act",
			"The Alberta Association of Chiefs of Police"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 14,
		"question": "The main duties of a security professional are to:",
		"correct": "Observe, deter, report",
		"options": [
			"Observe, notify, arrest ",
			"Observe, deter, report",
			"Concentrate, notice, recall ",
			"Contain, deter, arrest "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 15,
		"question": "When approached by media, you should: ",
		"correct": "Observe, deter, report",
		"options": [
			"Tell them “no comment”",
			"Ignore them",
			"Only provide “yes” or “no” answers ",
			"Refrain from participating in an interview"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 17,
		"question": "When approached by media, you should: ",
		"correct": "Refrain from participating in an interview",
		"options": [
			"Tell them “no comment”",
			"Ignore them",
			"Only provide “yes” or “no” answers ",
			"Refrain from participating in an interview"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 18,
		"question": "After you have called the police to assist with a hostile individual, you should: ",
		"correct": "Continue to monitor the individual and situation",
		"options": [
			"Continue on with your patrol duties ",
			"Continue to monitor the individual and situation",
			"Tell the individual to leave before the police arrive",
			"Ask the individual to provide you with a statement"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 19,
		"question": "Which of these is not appropriate to be contained in a notebook? ",
		"correct": "E-mail address of secretary",
		"options": [
			"Cell phone number of witness ",
			"E-mail address of secretary ",
			"Record of false alarm ",
			"Complaints from members of the public"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 20,
		"question": "When you have finished a notebook, you should: ",
		"correct": "Write the date of your last entry in the front  cover. ",
		"options": [
			"Shred it because it contains personal information ",
			"Tear out the pages with personal information and turn the remainder over to your supervisor ",
			"Write the date of your last entry in the front  cover. ",
			"Give it to the client for review "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 21,
		"question": "It is okay to add details to a statement if you know the information and the witness does not. ",
		"correct": "False",
		"options": ["True ", "False"]
	},
	{
		"id": 22,
		"question": "If you leave blank lines in your notebook, you should:",
		"correct": "Draw a single line through the blank and initial",
		"options": [
			"Shade in the blank area and initial",
			"Put an x through the blank line(s)",
			"Draw a single line through the blank and initial",
			"Initial the blank and indicate date and time"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 23,
		"question": "professionals in Alberta are licensed under the: ",
		"correct": "Security Services and Investigators Act",
		"options": [
			"a.	Security Services and Investigators Act",
			"b.	Security Services and Investigators Regulation ",
			"c.	Personal Property Security Act ",
			"d.	Security Management Regulation "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 24,
		"question": "Persons with any criminal record are not permitted to apply for a security licence in the province of Alberta.",
		"correct": "False",
		"options": ["a.	True ", "b.	False "]
	},
	{
		"id": 25,
		"question": "The Registrar may refuse the renewal of an individual security licence if: ",
		"correct": "The licensee fails to provide information as   required by the Act, regulations, or the Registrar",
		"options": [
			"a.	The licensee has not worked a minimum of 20 hours/week as a security professional ",
			"b.	The licensee fails to provide information as   required by the Act, regulations, or the Registrar",
			"c.	The licensee fails to complete basic first aid training ",
			" d.	The licensee is suspected of a criminal offence "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 26,
		"question": "  Public complaints against licensees are submitted in writing to:",
		"correct": "The owner of the business employing the subject of the complaint",
		"options": [
			"a. 	The local police department ",
			" b.	The Registrar of security licensees ",
			" c.	The owner of the business employing the subject of the complaint ",
			" d.	The individual against whom the complaint is being filed "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 27,
		"question": "With consent of both parties, an employer may attempt to resolve an issue between a security professional and a complainant.",
		"correct": "True",
		"options": ["a.	True ", "b.	False "]
	},
	{
		"id": 28,
		"question": "When a witness tells you they think they know who committed a crime, you should: ",
		"correct": "Make note of the name to pass along to the police",
		"options": [
			" a.	Make note of the name to pass along to the police ",
			" b.	Find the named person and arrest him or her ",
			"c.	Ask the witness to write the suspect’s name and number in your notebook ",
			" d.	Let the witness go since you know who the guilty party is "
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 29,
		"question": "What information is not required in your daily, opening notebook entry? ",
		"correct": "Make note of the name to pass along to the police",
		"options": [
			
a.	Weather 
b.	Name of partner 
c.	Special events 
d.	Expected visitors to the premises 

		]
	}
]
